Register of the Norwegian Subject Collection, 1949-1993.
Hoover Institution Archives
Norwegian Subject Collection,
1949-1993
XX813
5 manuscript boxes (2.1 linear feet)
Hoover Institution Archives Stanford, California 94305-6010
Election campaign literature, pamphlets, leaflets, and serial issues, relating to various aspects of Norwegian history, and especially to Norwegian politics and election campaigns.
Administrative Information
Access
Collection is open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Access Points
Norway--History.; Norway--Politics and government.; Elections--Norway.; Norway.
Series Description
- Subject File, 1949-1993. (Box Nos. 1-5.)
  Printed matter consisting mostly of campaign material of Norwegian political parties.
Container List
See card catalog for increments that may have been received after December 1994.
- SUBJECT FILE, 1949-1993
  - Miscellany, 1949-1993 (Box 1.)
  - Military, 1982
  - Peace movements, 1982
  - Political Parties. Printed matter
    - Anders Langes Parti, 1973
    - Arbeiderpartiet
      - 1965
      - 1969
      - 1973
      - 1977
    - Demokratiske sosialister partiet, 1973
    - Fedrelandspartiet, 1990 (Box 2.)
    - Fremskritt
      - 1977
      - 1993
    - Gronne, 1993
    - Hoyres
      - 1965
      - 1969
      - 1973
      - 1977
      - 1993
    - Kristelig folkeparti (Box 3.)
      - 1969
      - 1973
      - 1977
      - 1993
    - Kristent Konservativt Parti, 1992
    - Kvinnenes frei folkevalgte, 1972
    - Liberale Folkpartiet, 1993
    - Norges kommunistiske parti
      - 1963
      - 1965
      - 1973
      - 1977
    - Norske Arbeiderpartiet, 1993 (Box 4.)
    - Nye Folkepartiet, 1973-1977
    - Pensjonist Partiet, 1993
    - Rod Valgallianse
      - 1973
      - 1977
      - 1993
    - Samediggi, 1989
    - Samlingspartiet Ny Fremtid, 1993
    - Senterpartiet
      - 1965
      - 1969
      - 1973
      - 1977
      - 1993
    - Sosialistisk folkeparti (Box 5.)
      - 1965
      - 1969
      - 1973
    - Sosialistisk Valgforbund, 1973
    - Sosialistisk Venstre
      - 1977
      - 1993
    - Venstre
      - 1964
      - 1969
      - 1973
      - 1977
      - 1993